[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many solar segments are there in a year of the Chinese calendar?", "correct_answer": "24", "incorrect_answers": ["16", "6", "12"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the colloquial equivalent of the medical term Herpes zoster, which is used to define a condition, caused by the varicella zoster virus.", "correct_answer": "Shingles", "incorrect_answers": ["Cold sores", "Sementia", "Mumps"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 800 Philip IV the Fair of France was coronated by the Pope.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many stars are there on the flag of New Zealand?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["22", "6", "0"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do these places have in common: Wake Island, Johnston Atoll, Kingman Reef, Midway Island, Navassa, Baker Island and Jarvis Island?", "correct_answer": "They are uninhabited US possessions.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are a part of Nirvaau.", "They are UN controlled islands in the Atlantic.", "They are sites of famous WWII battles."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Egyptian city is the largest city not only in Africa, but also in the whole Middle East?", "correct_answer": "Cairo", "incorrect_answers": ["Alexandria", "Giza", "Ismailia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A combination lock has a  combination consisting of  three numbers. Each number could be 0,1,2,3,4,....39. How many different combinations are possible?", "correct_answer": "40 X 40 X 40=40^3", "incorrect_answers": ["40  X 3=120", "39X 3=117", "3 X3 X 3X.........=3^40"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The number Pi is larger than the number 4.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does John explain the scars on his hand when asked by the little girl in the 2004 action thriller movie Man on Fire?", "correct_answer": "He says it was a birth defect.", "incorrect_answers": ["He says a shark bit him.", "He does not answer and remains silent.", "He tells her he has no idea."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The largest natural karst crater on Earth - Ramon Crater, with a length of 40 km (25 miles) and width of 2 to 10 km (1.5 to 6 miles), is situated in the heart of this Middle East desert.", "correct_answer": "Negev desert", "incorrect_answers": ["Kyzyl Kum", "Judean Desert", "Mojave desert"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country is the largest producer of strawberries in the world according to 2007 data?", "correct_answer": "the USA", "incorrect_answers": ["Spain", "Russia", "Turkey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How fast can a domestic cat sprint?", "correct_answer": "30 MPH", "incorrect_answers": ["15 MPG", "17 MPH", "25 MPH"]}]